A Guide to the Luther Porter Jackson Papers, 1772-1960
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE
  - C. Personal 1918- 1960
    - Correspondence--Postcards 1947 (Box-folder 16:487)
    - Correspondence--Postcards 1948 (Box-folder 16:488)
    - Correspondence--Postcards 1949 (Box-folder 16:489)
    - Correspondence--Postcards 1950 (Box-folder 16:490)
- SERIES III. FINANCIAL & LEGAL
  - Bank Records 1928-1961 (Box-folder 17:491)
  - Bank Records 1940-1961 (Box-folder 17:492)
  - Bills-General 1928-1949 (Box-folder 17:493)
  - Contract 1928-1956 (Box-folder 17:494)
  - Copyright 1946 (Box-folder 17:495)
  - Medical Bills 1943 (Box-folder 17:496)
  - Personal Property Tax 1933-1949 (Box-folder 17:497)
  - Poll Tax 1923-1927 (Box-folder 17:498)
  - Red Circle Stores Stock 1946 (Box-folder 17:499)
  - School Bills 1911 (Box-folder 17:500)
  - School Bills 1912 (Box-folder 17:501)
  - School Bills 1913 (Box-folder 17:502)
  - School Bills 1914 (Box-folder 17:503)
  - (Box-folder 17:)
  - School Bills 1942 (Box-folder 17:504)
  - School Bills 1950 (Box-folder 17:505)
  - School Bills n.d. (Box-folder 17:506)
  - (Box-folder 17:)
  - Funeral Bills 1950 (Box-folder 17:507)
- SERIES IV. ORGANIZATIONAL AFFILIATIONS
  - A. The Virginia Teachers Voters League
    - The Virginia Voters League, Constitution n.d. (Box-folder 18:508)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Main Office 1935 (Box-folder 18:509)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Main Office 1936 (Box-folder 18:510)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Main Office 1937-39 (Box-folder 18:511)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Main Office 1940-41 (Box-folder 18:512)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Main Office 1942-43 (Box-folder 18:513)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Main Office 1944-45 (Box-folder 18:514)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Main Office 1946-49 (Box-folder 18:515)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Main Office n.d. (Box-folder 18:516)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Proposal n.d. (Box-folder 18:517)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Central Committee n.d. (Box-folder 18:518)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Rules n.d. (Box-folder 18:519)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Minutes 1934 (Box-folder 18:520)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Minutes 1941 (Box-folder 18:521)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Minutes 1943 (Box-folder 18:522)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Minutes 1948 (Box-folder 18:523)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Minutes 1949 (Box-folder 18:524)
    - The Virginia Voters League (Box-folder 18:)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Reports 1935, 1942 (Box-folder 18:525)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Reports 1944 (Box-folder 18:526)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Reports 1946 (Box-folder 18:527)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Reports 1946, 1948 (Box-folder 18:528)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Reports 1948 (Box-folder 18:529)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Financial Data 1935 (Box-folder 18:530)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Financial Data 1935-1936 (Box-folder 18:531)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Financial Data 1944 (Box-folder 18:532)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Financial Data 1948 (Box-folder 18:533)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Accomack County 1941-1942 (Box-folder 19:534)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Accomack County 1945-49 (Box-folder 19:535)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Albemarle County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 19:536)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Alleghany County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 19:537)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Amelia County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 19:538)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Amherst County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 19:539)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Appomattox County 1941-49 (Box-folder 19:540)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Arlington County 1941-49 (Box-folder 19:541)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Augusta County 1941-49 (Box-folder 19:542)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Bath County 1940-44 (Box-folder 19:543)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Bedford County 1940-1946 (Box-folder 19:544)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Bedford County 1948-1950 (Box-folder 19:545)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Bland County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 19:546)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Botetare County 1940-49 (Box-folder 19:547)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Buckingham County 1940-47 (Box-folder 19:548)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Buckingham County 1948-49 (Box-folder 19:549)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Buchanan County 1940-47 (Box-folder 19:550)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Brunswick County 1940-45 (Box-folder 19:551)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Brunswick County 1946-49 (Box-folder 19:552)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Campbell County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 20:553)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Caroline County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 20:554)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Carroll County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 20:555)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Charles City County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 20:556)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Charlotte County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 20:557)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Chesterfield County 1941-1945 (Box-folder 20:558)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Chesterfield County 1946-1949 (Box-folder 20:559)
    - The Virginia Voters League (Box-folder 20:)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Clarke County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 20:560)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Craig County 1940-1941 (Box-folder 20:561)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Culpepper County 1940-1945 (Box-folder 20:562)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Culpepper County 1946-1949 (Box-folder 20:563)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Cumberland County 1940-1946 (Box-folder 20:564)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Cumberland County 1947-1950 (Box-folder 20:565)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Dickelson County 1940-1943 (Box-folder 20:566)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Dinwiddie County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 20:567)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Dinwiddie County 1949-1950 (Box-folder 20:568)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Elizabeth City 1940-1949 (Box-folder 20:569)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Essex County 1940-1944 (Box-folder 20:570)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Essex County 1945-1950 (Box-folder 20:571)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Fairfax County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 21:572)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Faquier County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 21:573)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Floyd County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 21:574)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Fluvanna County 1941-1948 (Box-folder 21:575)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Fluvanna County 1949-1950 (Box-folder 21:576)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Franklin County 1939-1950 (Box-folder 21:577)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Frederick County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 21:578)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Giles County 1941-1944 (Box-folder 21:579)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Gloucester County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 21:580)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Goochland County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 21:581)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Grayson County 1940-1945 (Box-folder 21:581)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Green County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 21:582)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Greensville County 1940-1945 (Box-folder 21:583)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Halifax County 1941-1950 (Box-folder 21:584)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Hanover County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 21:585)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Henrico County 1940-1947 (Box-folder 21:589)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Henry County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 22:590)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Henry County 1949-1950 (Box-folder 22:591)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Highland County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 22:592)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Isle of Wright County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 22:593)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Isle of Wright County 1949 (Box-folder 22:594)
    - The Virginia Voters League, James City County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 22:595)
    - The Virginia Voters League, King George County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 22:596)
    - The Virginia Voters League, King and Queen County 1949-1948 (Box-folder 22:597)
    - The Virginia Voters League, King and Queen County 1949-1950 (Box-folder 22:598)
    - The Virginia Voters League, King William County 1941-1948 (Box-folder 22:599)
    - The Virginia Voters League, King William County 1949 (Box-folder 22:600)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Lancaster County 1940-1947 (Box-folder 22:601)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Lee County 1940-1941 (Box-folder 22:602)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Loudow County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 22:603)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Louisa County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 22:603a)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Louisa County 1949 (Box-folder 22:604)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Lunenberg County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 22:605)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Lunenberg County 1949-1950 (Box-folder 22:605a)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Madison County 1941-1948 (Box-folder 22:606)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Matthew County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 22:607)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Mecklenberg County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 22:608)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Mecklenberg County 1949 (Box-folder 23:609)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Middles County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 23:610)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Montgomery County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 23:611)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Nansemond County 1940-1946 (Box-folder 23:612)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Nansemond County 1947-1949 (Box-folder 23:613)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Nelson County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 23:614)
    - The Virginia Voters League, New Kent County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 23:615)
    - The Virginia Voters League, New Kent County 1949 (Box-folder 23:616)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Norfolk County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 23:617)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Northampton County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 23:618)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Northumberland County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 23:619)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Nottoway County 1940-1945 (Box-folder 23:620)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Nottoway County 1946-1950 (Box-folder 23:621)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Orange County 1940-1947 (Box-folder 23:622)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Orange County 1948-1949 (Box-folder 23:623)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Page County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 23:624)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Patrick County 1940-1941 (Box-folder 23:625)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Pittsylvania County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 24:626)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Powhatan County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 24:627)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Prince Edward County 1940-1947 (Box-folder 24:628)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Prince Edward County 1948-1949 (Box-folder 24:629)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Prince George County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 24:630)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Prince William County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 24:631)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Princess Anne County 1940-1946 (Box-folder 24:632)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Princess Anne County 1947-1949 (Box-folder 24:633)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Pulaski County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 24:634)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Rappahannock County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 24:635)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Richmond County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 24:636)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Roanoke County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 24:637)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Rockbridge County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 24:638)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Rockingham County 1941-1948 (Box-folder 24:639)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Russell County 1940-1947 (Box-folder 24:640)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Scott County 1940-1947 (Box-folder 24:641)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Shenandoah County 1940-1943 (Box-folder 24:642)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Smyth County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 24:643)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Southampton County 1941-1947 (Box-folder 24:644)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Southampton County 1949-1950 (Box-folder 24:645)
    - The ATA Correspondence 1964 Southampton 1964 (Box-folder 24:646)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Spotsylvania County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 24:647)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Stafford County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 24:648)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Surry County 1937-1948 (Box-folder 25:649)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Surry County 1949 (Box-folder 25:650)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Sussex County 1940-1947 (Box-folder 25:651)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Sussex County 1948-1950 (Box-folder 25:652)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Tazewell County 1940-1948 (Box-folder 25:653)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Warren County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 25:654)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Warrick County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 25:655)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Washington County 1940-1946 (Box-folder 25:656)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Westmoreland County 1940 (Box-folder 25:657)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Westmoreland County 1949 (Box-folder 25:658)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Wise County 1941-1949 (Box-folder 25:659)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Wythe County 1940-1949 (Box-folder 25:660)
    - The Virginia Voters League, York County 1940-1950 (Box-folder 25:661)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Alexandria City 1940-1949 (Box-folder 25:662)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Arlington City 1942-1949 (Box-folder 25:663)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Bristol City 1940-1948 (Box-folder 25:664)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Buena Vista City 1940-1949 (Box-folder 25:665)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Charlottesville City 1942-1949 (Box-folder 25:666)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Clifton City 1942-1949 (Box-folder 25:667)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Danville City 1940-1949 (Box-folder 25:668)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Fredericksburg City 1941-1949 (Box-folder 25:669)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Hampton City 1941-1944 (Box-folder 25:670)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Harrisonburg City 1940-1948 (Box-folder 25:671)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Hopewell City 1940-1949 (Box-folder 25:672)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Lynchburg City 1940-1949 (Box-folder 26:673)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Newport News City 1941-1949 (Box-folder 26:674)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Norfolk City 1939-1944 (Box-folder 26:675)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Norfolk City 1945-1949 (Box-folder 26:676)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Norfolk City 1945-1949 (Box-folder 26:677)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Petersburg City 1938-1949 (Box-folder 26:678)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Portsmouth City 1940-1948 (Box-folder 26:679)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Radford City 1940-1950 (Box-folder 26:680)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Richmond City 1945-1949 (Box-folder 26:681)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Roanoke City 1940-1949 (Box-folder 26:682)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Stauton City 1940-1950 (Box-folder 26:683)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Williamsburg City 1940-1948 (Box-folder 26:684)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Winchester City 1940-1949 (Box-folder 26:685)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Alpha. Kapppa. Alpha. 1941-1948 (Box-folder 26:686)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Alpha. Phi. Alpha. 1934-1947 (Box-folder 26:687)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Delta Sigma Theta 1941-1945 (Box-folder 26:688)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Intra-Fratenity Council n.d. (Box-folder 26:689)
    - The Virginia Voters League, Omega Psi Phi 1941-1945 (Box-folder 26:690)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records 1944-1948 (Box-folder 27:691)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records 1945-1947, n.d. (Box-folder 27:692)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records n.d. (Box-folder 27:693)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records n.d. (Box-folder 27:694)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records n.d. (Box-folder 27:695)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records 1932-1948 (Box-folder 27:696)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records 1948-1949 (Box-folder 27:697)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records n.d. (Box-folder 27:698)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records 1948 (Box-folder 27:699)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records 1949 (Box-folder 27:700)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records 1943 (Box-folder 27:701)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records 1949 (Box-folder 27:702)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records 1947-1948 (Box-folder 27:703)
    - The Virginia Voters League Records n.d. (Box-folder 27:704)
  - B. The Virginia Teachers Association Office of the "Civic Education Secretaries Office" 1941-1950
    - The Virginia Voters League Records 1941-42 (Box-folder 28:705)
    - The V. T. A. Civil Education Secretaries Office 1943 (Box-folder 28:706)
    - The V. T. A. Civil Education Secretaries Office 1944 (Box-folder 28:707)
    - The V. T. A. Civil Education Secretaries Office 1946 (Box-folder 28:708)
    - The V. T. A. Civil Education Secretaries Office 1949 (Box-folder 28:709)
    - The V. T. A. Civil Education Secretaries Office 1944 (Box-folder 28:710)
    - The V. T. A. Civil Education Jackson--Cooper 1942-1944 (Box-folder 28:711)
    - The V. T. A. Civil Education Jackson--Palmer 1942-1944 (Box-folder 28:712)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Palmer 1940, 1942 (Box-folder 28:713)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Palmer 1943 (Box-folder 28:714)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Picott 1944 (Box-folder 28:715)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Picott 1945 (Box-folder 28:716)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Picott 1946 (Box-folder 28:717)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson-- Picott 1947 (Box-folder 28:718)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Picott 1948 (Box-folder 28:719)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson-- Picott 1949 (Box-folder 28:720)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Palmer 1945 (Box-folder 28:721)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Picott 1943 (Box-folder 28:722)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson-- Picott 1944 (Box-folder 28:723)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Seay 1941 (Box-folder 28:724)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Seay 1942 (Box-folder 28:725)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Seay 1942 (Box-folder 28:726)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Seay 1943 (Box-folder 28:727)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Seay 1944 (Box-folder 28:728)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--Union 1942, 1943 (Box-folder 28:729)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--General 1940-1947 (Box-folder 28:730)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Jackson--General 1948-1949 (Box-folder 28:731)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Accomoke County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 29:732)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Albermarle County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 29:733)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Alleghany County 1948 (Box-folder 29:734)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Amelia County 1940, 1948 (Box-folder 29:735)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Amherst County 1946, 1948 (Box-folder 29:736)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Appomattox County 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 29:737)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Augusta County 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 29:738)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Bedford County 1946 (Box-folder 29:739)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education (Box-folder 29:)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Bland County 1944, 1949 (Box-folder 29:740)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Botetourt County 1948, 1949 (Box-folder 29:741)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Blaneswick County 1948 (Box-folder 29:742)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Buchanam County 1942 (Box-folder 29:743)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Buckingham County 1940, 1948 (Box-folder 29:744)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Campbell County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 29:745)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Caroline County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 29:746)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Carroll County 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 29:747)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Charles City County 1940 (Box-folder 29:748)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Charlotte County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 29:749)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Chesterfield County 1942, 1949 (Box-folder 29:750)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Clarke County 1942 (Box-folder 29:751)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Craig County 1950 (Box-folder 29:752)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Culpepper County 1940, 1948 (Box-folder 29:753)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Cumberland County 1942, 1949 (Box-folder 29:754)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Dickerson County 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 29:755)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Dinwiddle County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 29:756)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Essex County 1944, 1948 (Box-folder 29:757)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Fairfax County 1948-1949 (Box-folder 29:758)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Fluvanna County 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29:759)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Fauquier County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 29:760)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Floyd County 1942, 1946 (Box-folder 29:761)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Franklin County 1940, 1944 (Box-folder 29:)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Frederick County 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 29:763)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Glouchester County 1943, 1948 (Box-folder 29:764)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Goochland County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 29:765)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Grayson County 1942 (Box-folder 29:766)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Greene County 1948 (Box-folder 29:768)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Greensville County 1942-1944 (Box-folder 29:769)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Halifax County 1942, 1949 (Box-folder 29:770)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Hanover County 1944, 1948 (Box-folder 29:771)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Hendrico County 1943, 1948 (Box-folder 29:772)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Henry County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 29:773)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Highland County 1944, 1950 (Box-folder 29:774)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Isle of Wright 1948, 1950 (Box-folder 29:775)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education James City County 1942 (Box-folder 29:776)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education King George County 1942, 1949 (Box-folder 29:777)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education King & Queen County 1948 (Box-folder 29:778)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education King William County 1946, 1950 (Box-folder 29:779)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Lancaster County 1940, 1948 (Box-folder 30:780)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Lee County 1944 (Box-folder 30:781)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Loudoun County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 30:782)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Louisa County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 30:783)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Lunenberg County 1948 (Box-folder 30:784)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Matthews County 1944, 1948 (Box-folder 30:785)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Mecklenburg County 1942, 1949 (Box-folder 30:786)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Middlesex County 1948 (Box-folder 30:787)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Montgomery County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 30:788)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Nansemond County 1940, 1949 (Box-folder 30:789)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Nelson County 1942, 1950 (Box-folder 30:790)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education New Kent County 1940, 1948 (Box-folder 30:791)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Norfolk County 1947 (Box-folder 30:792)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Northumberland County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 30:793)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Northampton County 1942, 1949 (Box-folder 30:794)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Nottoway County 1942, 1948 (Box-folder 30:795)
    - The V.T.A. Civil Education Orange County 1940, 1944 (Box-folder 30:796)